Place the logs properly,
Now its caught fire.
Alright then,
who’s going to tell a story today?
Laddu…you were late.
You tell a story.
Bro…
I don’t know any stories….
But when you mention being late,
I remember this thing
3-4 days ago,
a new boy joined our school.
Oye leave the bicycle!
Run!
Hey…hello…..yes you!
Come here.
COME HERE!
What are the school timings?
- 9.
9 o’clock?
School starts at 9, eh?!
We just happen to like arriving
half an hour early, don’t we?
Now then….let me set
your watch right…c’mon now!
C’mon…
move along!
Alright….the last chapter
is now done. Syllabus complete!
Sir…
May I come in?
And who are you?
Sir, new admission.
It’s my first day today.
New admission?!
In September?
Bro, you aren’t just late for the class;
You are late for school (year) too!
Sir, actually I have
come from very far.
Are you coming from another planet
that you are reaching in September?!
HEYY!!!
Get in!
And raise your hands and stand!
Look son…the horses who lag behind
end up getting whipped the most.
And then only do
they run in the race.
C’MON! Now you all get ready too.
Let’s revise the first chapter.
So tell me…The Battle of Plassey was
fought between who and who?
Chanakya…!
Sorry sir…haven’t been
able to do any revision.
This is the state in
the first chapter itself…
Well, get ready for some ‘service’.
Sir! Sir!
Hey!
You keep both your hands raised!
And you, bring forth your hand.
Sir! Sir!...Sir, it was fought between
the East India Company and the Nawab of Bengal.
When?
- Sir, 23 June, 1757.
Who won?
- East India Company.
Vidwaan took this to heart.
[Dramatically] “Who was the first to
establish their capital at Delhi?”
He kept shooting arrows
of question after question…
“Tomar Rajputs.”
And the new boy…
shot arrows of answers
As if our classroom turned
into the battlefield of Plassey!
All is fair in love and war…
so Vidwaan gradually
stooped down to cheating.
“After whom is
the country of ‘Bhaarat’ named?”
“This is out of syllabus!!!”
“After King Bharat.”
Vidwaan’s arrow turned to ash!
And for the first time,
we saw him smile.
“God you are great!”
“Hail Lord Ram!”
And after that,
there was one attack after another!
But the boy didn’t give up.
He fought; and he won
The whole class had realized that
there was something special about him.
But there was one problem…
He’s too proud.
He thinks we are not equal to him.
Poor thing’s shy.
He used to keep to himself;
didn’t talk to anyone.
And the class began to feel
- What if he is an ISI agent?
There was a bit of a suspense.
I took it for a couple of days,
but by the 3rd day,
I couldn't take it anymore.
No mom…I am not feeling hungry.
I’ll eat later.
He’s started worrying
about his studies.
Yeah sure…Worry!
Must have eaten something outside.
I thought, now this
can’t continue like this.
Churan (herbal digestive)...
it sharpens the mind!
But yours already is.
Thanks.
Coming for lunch?
- No, I have my lunch at home.
After lunch, we will
be going to the canteen;
...to have samosas.
Wanna come?
No. Revision is still left.
Good!
Bro, come straight
to the point already!
Why are you messing
with our digestion?
That day I had sworn
on Goddess Kali…
…that, today I’ll find out for sure.
Why don’t you talk to anyone?
No…nothing like that.
The whole class says…
- What?
…that you’re an ISI agent.
- Are you ?
Then ?
It’s a long story,
shall I tell you tomorrow?
And yes, come a bit early.
I cannot tell it in front of everyone.
New Caption
There’s still an hour for school to start.
I know! I know!
But I can’t study well at home.
the mood to study
is best right here.
Sure you won’t tell anyone?
Else it will be trouble.
Trouble?
You won’t tell,
would you?
Not at all! You assume that
I never even heard it.
Even if by mistake if anyone found out…
I swear on Vidya (knowledge);
on Dharti Mata (mother Earth)
swear on Bhagwan (God)...
won’t tell anyone.
Then ?
What is your age?
- 18.
19.
Yours?
- 20.
And yours ?
- 19.
Sorry bro, I won’t be able
to tell you anything further;
else there will be trouble.
Damn, then why did
you tell us all this?
Told you by mistake.
Now you will have to
tell us the whole thing.
Sorry friends,
don’t force me.
Alright,
we’ll meet tomorrow.
How will you run away ?
Catch him...
Every 2-3 months,
I have to change schools.
We cannot stay at one place for long.
And we don’t tell this to anyone either.
And if someone found
out where we live…
Hey Bro! Planning to
blow up the school or what?!
If anyone found out,
then Earth could get attacked!
Attack?!
Ours is not a normal family.
My grandpa has some powers.
What powers?
Hey!
Stand up!
What’s your problem?
Neither do you study yourself
nor do you let anyone else study.
Get out!
Sir, just a minute.
What kind of power?
HEY!
Didn’t you hear…get out!
Bro tell me,
what kind of power?
[with reverb]
Superpower!
My grandpa has superpowers.
As in…he can fly in the air
as high as he wishes…
…can lift loads as heavy as can be.
Like Superman?
That’s my Grandpa for you.
Superman?
- Superhero.
We just doesn’t tell anyone.
Has to remain a secret.
He takes great responsibility;
must use his powers for the right,
else the powers will be lost.
Whenever there’s a fight,
he hits so much that one loses count;
the aliens shiver on his mention.
Grandpa is famous across
planets far far away.
He has a bounty of
crores on his head.
When alien kids don’t sleep at night;
you know what their mothers tell them?
You better sleep kid.
or what?
The Great Grand Superhero will come!
The Great Grand Superhero!
Part A: The Arrival of the Aliens
Wow Dude!
This should be known to the whole class,
the whole school, the whole town!
No bro, it can’t be revealed.
If we told anyone,
then powers are lost.
What happened?
Oh we are done for!
Why?
- But you told me everything!
No bro, powers are not lost
if it's told to kids.
The issue is for ages 18 and above.
If elders are told,
then the powers are lost.
Okay bye!
See you tomorrow.
I am coming too
to see your home.
My home is quite far.
Tch! What do I have to do!
Studies will be taken care of by you
and the battles by Grandpa.
I am tension-free!
We are staying here; for now,
so that no one gets suspicious.
Alright, bye!
Deepu!
- Yeah?
Thanks!
Why ?
Your Grandpa is such a big Superhero
and still you made me your friend.
Hey Deepu…
Deepu... you arrived right on time son.
Come here,
take this bucket inside.
Back’s busted.
C’mon now, come down.
Come now.
There’s a lizard inside.
- WHAT?!
Hey…hey listen…
I’d shooed it off yesterday.
If you had shooed it off then
how come it’s back?!
Grandpa, I am very tired.
I understand you are tired.
But if the water gets cold,
then you’ll have to heat it and bring it again.
I won’t go.
You will have to bring it.
Come come,
come now, son.
Shoo! Shoo! Go!
Go!
It’s gone.
Gone?
- YES.
Gone out?
- Yes! Yes!
You sure?
- Next time I will take a camera inside.
His slippers are worn out and old.
His story has never been told.
He is the protector of every lane.
Every galaxy echoes his name.
Why are you afraid of lizards?
It’s a long story.
Once my father had Malaria…
platelets down,
was almost about to die.
Then I decided...
He will make you weep !
One hell of a guy, this dude.
Enemies your grandpa’s “in the hood”.
Transcending every storm...
Shattering every norm...
The bird soars in fight
The mosquitoes were terrorized.
They packed their bahs and fled.
And this caused a tension among the lizards.
Their kids were starving to death.
Hope has found its way...
Troubles have no place to say
He thinks
“Can all this be true ?”
It might feel like a dream to him too.
ATTACK!
And since then you
have been scared of lizards?
Naah…
it’s a long story.
Hey, hey!
If you wish to know the story then listen
to the whole story, else don’t ask!!
Same old stories,
repeated again and again...
Everybody understood...?
Sir…
May I come in?
Be punctual!
Everyone... Chapter 21,
Couplets by Rahim.
Open your books, first couplet is...
Rahim says, do not disregard
or throw away insignificant things
just because you see important things.
A sword cannot replace a needle
where a needle is needed.
HEY!!
The class is happening on this side;
what are you looking there for?
Look forward.
Bro, you didn’t tell anyone;
did you?
Don’t worry, everyone is
below the age of 18.
It’s not that…what if someone blurts it
out to a teacher or family member?
I have made them anty-shanty promise.
Understood kids?
The aliens were terrorized.
Wherever they went, there was Grandpa.
And then Grandpas said-
‘Son! I’ll have to treat you differently.
You won’t get it this way.’
Then he grabbed him like this
and dragged him to his own planet
and then a punch here and a punch there.
Punch here…punch there….
It’s further ahead…
Made a full rail (train) of him…
what did he make?
[in chorus] Train!
Then?
The alien said-
‘Sorry Grandpa’.
Grandpa said-
‘Nope. Today you are done for son!’
Was there gravity there?
Yo…gravity is for people like us,
not for Superheroes!
When the Superhero arrives,
science is left behind.
Got it?!
[chorus mumbling] Hmmmm
HEY!
Get out!!
All of you get out!
That’s it; that day the aliens had
sworn that they would come back.
And they are to arrive today.
The battle must have started already.
Roosters!!
Will you ever get back to class
or will you lay eggs here itself!
GET BACK!!
C’MON!
Superhero has a principle.
The one who punches first,
is the one who wins.
He who is protected by God
cannot be killed by anyone!
Grandpa has sworn that he will
deal with them for once and all.
Whoa!!!
Then he must get wounded as well, right?
Bones get crushed!
But then, what to do?
That’s the job of a Superhero.
If there’s power,
there’s pain.
At least now stop your
war against the lizard!
You got away this time!
What if it got fractured?
And at this age,
even surgery is not possible.
I am prescribing some medicines.
You must rest for a few days now.
And yes, do not lift
any kind of weight.
Is that mine?
- Yes. It is yours.
For him.
Dad,
we’ll head home?
Bye !
We are also coming!
Will get to meet Grandpa!
Bro, if Grandpa finds out that...
I have told you guys,
then he will parcel me to another planet.
Don’t worry!
We will not come near your home.
We will just glance from far away.
No one will be suspicious.
[in chorus]
Yes, yes! Correct!
You go in,
we will see from outside.
Are you sure,
this is his house?
Yes, this is the one he had told me.
Where is the Superhero? Alien?
Wait bro..they will come.
Superhero?
- On a scooter?
Superhero On a scooter?
Shouldn’t he be flying in?
Looks like he’s returning from a fight.
C’mon guys….
you have to leave.
There has been an attack.
The aliens are here.
They threw a train on Grandpa’s hand.
Bro, if we could be of any help,
then do let us know.
God help us…
You won’t be able to
do anything. Now leave!!
[News on TV] The situation
in Delhi is bad today as well.
Pollution is in dire straits.
As you can see, pollution is spreading like
an epedemic, it’s symptoms are everywhere.
Papa, has there been any news of a train?
No. What was it supposed to be?
As in, someone might
have thrown a train.
Did you do anything?
- Oh no! Was asking just like that.
Tell me the truth.
If you caused trouble
then I will break your teeth!
That’s why aliens come here.
They know!
It’s them who cause trouble
and some innocent gets blamed.
[On TV] Hello friends!
We have got big news.
The Railway ministry has decided to
increase the fares per 20 kms by 1 rupee;
80 paise for long distance trains
and 1 rupee 30 paise for AC trains.
In response to this decision...
protests have been see
in many places across the country.
Today, some anti-social elements have tried
to vandalize trains and railway stations.
What problem do the aliens
have with the railway fares?
Alright, you take care.
I will be back in two days.
Where are you going?
Delhi. Alright...
I’ll miss my train…
Oh no Dad!
Don’t go there. It’s dangerous.
They are throwing trains there.
Throwing trains?! Who?
- Aliens!!
[laughing] Aliens!!
No Dad…I won’t let you go!
Hey...!!
Won’t let you go!
C’mon let go!
I’ll miss my train! Let go!
Won’t let you go!
Son, I am getting late
for my train….let go!
Dad…there are aliens there!!
Hey, let go!
Have you gone mad!!
Let go!
I’ll miss my train! Let go!
I’ll get a chocolate for you.
Last night I watched all the news channels;
read every newspaper
but your train news was mentioned nowhere!
It’s all about pollution,
pollution, pollution.
What do you think...?
the Superhero and alien
battle happens in a boxing ring?
The fights are so fearsome that...
even they don’t realize
where they start to fight
and where they reach
- one country to another
from the Earth to Mars, Moon, Jupiter.
Grandpa deliberately took
them to another planet,
so that we,
WE don’t face any trouble.
A person is doing so much for us
and we are looking for evidence?!
C’mon now!
What’re you saying!?
Sorry bro!
Please don’t tell this to Grandpa
He’ll be hurt.
Here…your newspapers!
May I come in, Sir ?
Why was everyone clapping?
This is Chingi.
Her father was in the Army.
She and her father were going somewhere
when a terrorist shot at her father.
He fired back too.
But soon he ran out of bullets.
Chinki saw a gun a little way away.
When she went to pick it up,
the terrorist shot at her leg.
Really ?
- Yes.
It was in the newspapers too!
Next chapter- CLIMATE.
Hello.
- Hello.
May I help you?
No-no…
I’ll take care of it. Thank you.
I’ll help!
C’mon! Attack!
Shall I ring the bell?
Will you write an application for this?
Just ring!
We... notebook
Err…we..Deepu friends…class same.
Namaste. We are Deepu’s friends;
from the same class.
Deepu had forgotten his notebook
and we are here to return it.
To return just one notebook
the whole class is here!
Very good!
I was in the middle of cleaning.
Will just wrap it up and come.
Just wait for 2 mins.
I will be down.
What happened?
You had forgotten your notebook.
Oh…okay…thank you, bye !
See you tomorrow in school.
What now?
Umm…Superhe…
Grandpa had said to meet before leaving.
Oh yes, I know. But he’s asked
you to come back later.
Here was a bit of an emergency
so he’s taken off directly from the terrace itself.
Okay…Bye!
We got late by just a little, bro.
Hey Deepu! Open the door.
Your friends are here.
Shhh…!!!
[whispering] Come come…
- What ?
Come.
- Hey..!
Look at all their faces carefully;
scan them.
They will follow you in the alleys, at the bus-stand,
at the train-station, on the road; everywhere!
Will investigate you!
Why ?
I have sung your praises
a lot in front of them.
What praises?
That you have a lot of strength;
you can do anything!
What all can I do?
You can fly in the air;
lift very heavy objects;
aliens-who live on other planets-
you can beat them up;
in a nutshell- you are a Superhero!
Like Superman!
Do they believe you?
That’s why they are standing here.
If I tell them that you are fighting with
the aliens now and will be back at night,
then they will remain
standing here till night.
What?
One has to brag a little, else
In spite of studying
so much and well, no one takes you seriously.
Now you have to keep it in your mind that
you are a superhero; a Superhero!
I’ll be back after
sending them away.
Hey hey hey….
who told you that I am?
What?
A..err…Superhero.
Oh it’s an old trick to
get settled in a new school.
I AM a Superhero!
That’s it…very good!
If you meet them, then say the same thing
but with a little more confidence.
I REALLY AM!
But don’t tell anyone or
I will lose my powers!
Already told!
So powers gone!
Kids knowing is not a worry;
it’s the adults-
age 18 and above is the issue.
I said the same in class too!!
I really am;
I am telling you I AM!
Very good!
Say it with this same confidence. Bravo!
Hey…I AM!
Hey…
Still here?
What if the fight ends earlier;
that’s why we were waiting.
Bro, many times the
fights last for months!
Now scram!
It’s Vidwan sir’s test tomorrow...
let’s leave.
Deepu…whether you believe
it or not, I am a Superstar!
Superhero.
- Ya ya…Superhero.
Okay, I believe you.
Thank You.
Other than you, can anyone else
say that you are a Superhero.
Your grandma knows.
How did Grandma die?
Alien attack?
Mmmm…she got pneumonia.
Any other evidence or witness,
who is alive; other than you?
Yes, there is. There is a picture…
I have with my alien friend.
Show me.
This is my childhood picture.
That I know,
but where is the alien?
Right here, next to me.
But that’s an empty space.
Ya ya…alien is not visible in pictures.
You feel you are a superhero, right?
I don’t just feel, I AM !
Okay.
What okay?
Jump all the way till here and
I will believe that you are a Superhero.
Where? Till the spot
you are standing? There?
Yes.
What’s the big deal in that?
I can jump…
Umm…seems a bit too far.
How about till here?
Ohh…will have to practice.
It seems, there’s a different way
for him to come out.
Heyy…the door just opened.
It’s him? Looks too young to be his grandpa!
Let’s go…we will resume tomorrow.
[recording playing] We are seeking God.
Raju, I will be back in a little while.
and don’t leave the shop on him.
- [recording playing] God doesn’t only lives temple.
- God resides within us...
Please get me this stuff.
[recording playing] …we just have to open the eyes
of our mind... and God will appear before us…
Dear God!!
Hey…not this adulterated stuff.
Get the good stuff from inside.
This is a special customer.
Namaste !
- Namaste !
Your total is 430/-.
- HEY!!
What are you saying?!
Who can take money from you?!
All of this is yours only.
Please take it dear God, please.
Hey, how old are you?
- 22.
Go inside.
You do so much for us for free;
how can I charge you money?
If you allow, can I call
the rest of the ‘devotees’ too;
They wanted to see you.
Trees and plants were on earth
long before humans came.
Every tree has a story of their own...
- Oh Grandpa...
We want to listen to the ‘other’ stories!
- Yes yes, i will tell...
Your friends!
So…how have things been?
Ohh. All good.
You must have to do so
much running around, right?
Oh that’s alright.
How can you do all that at this age?
Oh they are asking about
that Superhero thing;
I have told them
that you are a Superhero.
Now whoever has any doubts,
please ask one by one.
Respected Superhero Grandpa!
Whatever you have done for us,
for that I express my gratitude.
Claps!!
Very good!
Now come straight to the question.
Do you also have to go No. 2?
Relevant questions please.
Why do superheroes wear briefs?
Why are the powers lost
if this is told to everyone?
When is the next battle?
Leave these all be, today just tell us
how you became a superhero.
When I was your age...
...I met Musi.
She had come that night to visit Earth,
along with her parents.
They liked the greenery here.
I stepped forward for a closer look.
...and she offered her hand for friendship.
...and then there was light.
I used to play a lot with her.
I used to get those candies for her.
Orange candies.
But I won’t tell anyone.
Neither did she.
One day, her mom-dad saw us.
Then, was there an attack?
- No.
They took her away.
Musi cried a lot as she was leaving.
I cried a lot too.
Then she never came back.
Musi !
Alien, my friend !
That’s it!
- Yes!
Then how did you become a superhero?
C’mon…as she was leaving
Musi left me powers too!
And since then, in her memory,
I maintain cleanliness and keep planting trees.
And when did you fight the first battle?
Aah…never got a chance.
And then there were so many battles
that he never got a chance to count them.
Yeahhh…
Can you show us a stunt
or something superhero like,
so that we could believe
that you are truly a superhero?
Oh! Mom’s here.
You can listen to the stories later;
have juice first.
So…..what did you
think of today’s session?
What was that you were saying?
- What ?
That you didn’t even
get a chance to fight.
Want to get me into trouble?
- Oh…what did I say wrong then?
Since the powers have come,
nothing has happened
No aliens, no fights.
Only when the aliens come,
then can I show the powers, right?
And what if
the aliens don’t come?
Then powers wasted! Hail the lord!
Peace! Bye-bye! Ta-ta!
Then how will you prove?
- What?
That you are a superhero.
What?
- Come here.
With stories!
Till the aliens arrive,
keep spinning stories about your bravery.
and when they do arrive,
then show your bravery for real! Simple!
Oh…avoid this love story.
Me-Musi-Orange candies!
Tell them something which has
fighting, explosions, battles, destruction.
That’s what trends these days.
You want to be a superhero,
but your stories are all cotton candy fluff.
The more humans spread trash,
the sooner the aliens will land.
Their new mission’s name
is Clean Earth Mission.
Wow!
Now aliens will clean up the earth?
No! They will clean us up from the earth.
That’s why they are attacking.
Then, when will the fight be?
Now, that’ll depend on the aliens,
whatever their plan will be.
[in chorus] Hmmm.
All that’s fine, but tell your
Grandpa that till there’re no fights,
at least show us
a costume of the superhero.
Need to get this made.
Oho…this that one right,
which swims in the air and somesaults…
kids watch him on TV.
- Yeah…he’s a superhero.
Will definitely be done
- Hmm.
Give me the measurement of the kid.
- Kid?
Yes; you need this for
the kid’s fancy dress, right?
Oh no-no…
I need this for myself.
Umm…then you need
this brief also made?
Yes! Everything is to be made.
Even the dupatta (cloak) at the back needs to be made.
Sir, with this picture,
can someone else’s picture be joined?
Absolutely Grandpa!
Rekha-Madhuri-Sonali, whoever you wish
to be joined with, we’ll get it joined!
No, no.
- More real than real itself!
Umm…err..the one which
flies in from other planets…
Alien ?
- Alien.
Can we have it, in my picture,
standing next to me? like this.
Oh Grandpa!! We can even
have it dance next to you!
It will look like the aliens had come to the Earth
to just have their picture taken with you.
Grandpa…should I put an Indian alien
or a Chinese or an American one?
Oh but aliens are from out of Earth, right?
But Grandpa, different types of aliens come
to India and different to America.
Then make it native, Indian.
Yes, yes !
- Thank you.
Bro, what a beating that was... super fun.
They were acting smart...
Umm…bathroom?
- Yes, that way but the flush doesn’t work.
See, I am definitely a superhero.
- Hmmm.
But looking at their enthusiasm,
I am a bit nervous.
If the alien doesn’t show up…
Till then Dad will get transferred.
Why are you getting tense?
Look Grandpa, you just keep
passing the time like this…
…you have got your fans and
my reputation will be secured too.
Grandpa, I have marketed you a lot!
Please don’t mess it up.
- [Sigh]
Come, let’s take you around a bit.
Where?
- Just come!
You must fly even higher, right?
This should be nothing for you!
Yo! Hello!
Raju said that you gave stuff from
the shop for free to someone.
Sorry dad.
I can’t tell you a lot.
But he’s a very useful guy.
Let me know if someone’s
causing you any trouble.
Will get them set!
Right now son,
I am troubled by you!
Stop ! Where are you going ?
Stop !
Poor guy…
Now how am I to explain
what’s happening outside.
So… if we wanted to be
superheroes like you,
then what should we do?
That I will tell you.
Pay attention…
When the aliens come,
woo their daughter and say-
‘Hey Senorita! I don’t want love…I want power!’
Hey hey hey…
wanna get killed or what?
You can’t become superheroes like that.
If you want to be a superhero...
...then exercise, build your body, eat well,
grow trees and plants,
breathe deep, serve your parents...
Maintain cleanliness,
help everyone, be useful to all...
that’s how to become a superhero.
Got it?
Exposing is not my job
but my habit.
Till he doesn’t reach the root of it,
he keeps at it-
Exposé King, Kannu!
Clean, Clear and Candid.
Dad !
Yes.
- Tell me something.
How does one do an exposé?
Interesting question.
The person you are suspicious of;
first listen to them fully.
Then whatever seems off to you,
investigate them one by one.
Then, question after question;
question after question- keep asking.
They will get trapped on their own.
Tell us something Grandpa…
- Yes?
When the aliens come,
then how would we know?
One can see a blue light
coming down from the sky.
Amazing!
Which movie is this from. ?
Oh brother!
It will come; hasn’t come yet
[all laugh]
Make one spicy…
extra chilli!
How many times?
Fourth.
- Fifth.
Very good! Why not have
some more junk food.
You have no control over your taste buds.
This is not the age for
indulging in junk food.
What happened?
Sixth time.
Chanakya.
- Absent!
Saksham.
Sachin.
- Absent!
Sunil.
Absent! Absent !
Absent!
Doctor! No needle please…
aren’t there any pills
instead of this?
I’ll die sir…
am not used to this…
You’ll have instant relief…
…what instant relief!?
My life will fly out!
Doctor…sir sir..please
Dad…don’t create
a scene here please!
Nothing will happen to you!
I am not creating a scene.
When I don’t want a needle then
why are you all forcing me.
Please hold him down.
You are a superhero Grandpa…
c’mon take it!
Oh I am not a superhero!
Hold him down!
- No no no….
- I don’t want a needle
then why are you all forcing me
Nothing will happen to you.
- What nothing will happen!!!!
What a patient!
- AAARGGHHHH!!!
Was it you who
was shouting inside?
Both of them are making fools
out of us. There’s no superhero.
Listen bro, this is a
‘Gangadhar is Shaktimaan’ situation.
They all are just like this.
But when the aliens come,
then their avatar will change-
And it will be the awesome Superhero one!
Let’s see…when will this
‘awesome Superhero’ be visible!
Tell me one thing...
You get hurt by an injection;
You are scared of heights,
scared of the dark…
I am not scared of the dark.
I can’t see in the dark
I am afraid of falling.
And then you claim
that you are a superhero.
When the aliens come...
...then I will show you what
kind of a superhero I am!
And the aliens are
never going to come.
They WILL...
My heart says that they will come.
They are aliens…
not ‘Karan Arjun’ that they will come.
O Dear Lord….either you
send those aliens down here
or call me up to you!
Why don’t they believe it?
Sorry God…for bothering
you this late in the night.
Please send a couple of aliens.
Grandpa is getting old.
Poor guy is a superhero and
still letting himself be disrespected.
Now YOU must do something.
Please.
I have stolen this from dad.
Don’t worry,
I will return it once I start earning.
Good Night.
Take care.
May I help you with something?
No dear, it’s not that heavy.
In that case,
let me help a little bit then.
What will you do with these plants?
These…
Oh I keep planting these.
After all, plants are our superpower!
By the way,
which school do you study in?
In Adarsh Vidyalay Mandir.
Oh! Our Deepu also studies there!
You are Deepu’s Grandpa?
- Yes.
That means you are the superhero?
I have heard your stories.
Really ?
Can I get superpowers too?
What will YOU do with superpowers?
You see, I want to stand
on my feet by myself;
that too without any support.
If there’s no trash,
then how will the aliens arrive?
and only when the aliens arrive,
will we know about the superhero.
The first time,
mom-dad had landed right here.
That’s why the large crater.
Now see, it’s full of water;
such a beautiful lake.
Yes...
Are you new here?
Have never seen you before.
- Yes. Just landed.
Umm…from where?
You see the moon there…
…which is left from the moon,
after 5 lakh kilometers a right...
and then after two planets left again.
From there.
Your identity?
We can fly,
can live for years without eating,
can speak in any language…
He just wants to
know who you are.
Ohh sorry! We are…
…You won’t tell anyone,
will you?
We are aliens.
We have come from another planet.
Huh?
- Don’t tell anyone.
Are you here for
someone’s wedding?
- No.
There’s going to be an attack on Earth.
We are here in that regard…
Here, there are trees, hills,
water, clouds, aquatic life…
Pure khadi!
The tailor said that just a couple
of washes and it will be perfect!
And a few push ups,
tummy goes and chest comes out!
Very Good !
- Thank You.
Do one thing;
hang this costume on the terrace.
The aliens will never come to earth then.
And which superhero
has a half-sleeve costume?!
Oh… the tailor ran out of cloth
so he made it half-sleeved.
and by the way…
This is the alien?
- Yes!
This is Jaadu!!
The whole world has watched the film!
Oh! I didn’t see this!
What happened?
Why are you shouting?
He thinks of himself as a superhero.
[sneakily] Powers will be lost.
- What ?
He thinks he is a superhero.
Yes.
He is a superhero.
That too the greatest superhero!
Is it?
Which battle did he fight?
The battles of Life.
When he was very young,
my grandpa passed away.
Along with his mother,
he took responsibility for the whole household.
He would help his mother at the shop.
Went to school barefeet.
He began to earn while still studying.
Got his mother treated
with his own hard work.
Built a house.
Got his sisters married.
He is such a simple man that
he has not even killed an ant till date.
Son, all of these only
a superhero can accomplish.
Love you dad!
That’s my grandpa.
He used to be a boxer.
Did you tell him about Deepu’s grandpa?
Should I?
What if his powers are lost?
It’s all lies.
Grandpa…
- Say Grand Father!
Grandfather,
do you think superheroes exist?
Don’t you see me?!
Can you fly?
Have you fought battles?
Even the crow flies.
And as of battles,
I have fought many.
There’s a boy in our class.
He says, his grandpa is a superhero!
Power’s gone!
So…tell me now.
Who’s that in your class who plays a hero?
- Deepu’s grandpa.
He says his grandpa can fly,
pick up trains.
Did he show you any of this?
- No.
Get him to box with me once.
Then he will never say
that he is a superpower.
Grandpa doesn’t fight with humans.
What if they get hurt badly?
It will be a mess.
He’s a boxing champion dude.
He’s beaten up many people.
He’s boxed at the national level.
Bro…he’s beaten up aliens.
He’s at the Universal level.
What are you saying!
You can eat…don’t worry.
Eat, eat!
Grandpa…our costume and
picture ideas don’t seem to be working.
So, let’s let them go.
Yeah…I didn’t like them either.
We would have been caught.
That’s why I am not going
to pay full price for them either.
Grandpa, I have a great idea!
- Tell me.
You will have to fight a little with
Saksham’s grandfather, as in boxing.
Once you defeat him
we will have nothing to worry about.
Whether aliens come or not,
you don’t have to worry.
I’ll prove that you are a superhero
and that’s that.
I think you will fight just fine.
We have fixed the match
with Kartar Singh on Sunday.
So do your exercises.
- Yo ! That Kartar...
haven’t you seen how huge his hands are.
Wanna get me killed?!
Seems like you have
put a bounty on my head!
Keep your confidence up.
Start exercising from tomorrow morning.
Look here Grandpa, you have caused this mess
and now you only will have to sort this out.
Now stop having this Laddu.
Have something healthy instead.
Gobbling laddus!
Son, put my name down.
I wanna build my body.
Why do you want to build
your body Grandpa?
Have to fight a battle.
Hey…how long will it take
to get strength like him?
Aren’t you the kids’ superstar Grandpa?
- Yes.
You must have heard of
the boxing match then.
Yes yes…that friendly match
that the kids have organized.
Well, it’s friendly to speak of
but we will play it seriously.
Seriously; okay.
C’mon! Do it!
You can do it!
The kids have
high expectations from you.
Wow! Uprooted it!!!
Look bro,
that’s how the Earth people fight!
Hello sister!
Did you find the superhero?
No sister.
We haven’t been able to track him.
So we had come to watch a Sunny Deol film.
What action!
- C’mon hero!! Hit the villain!
Have you gone nuts!
The force has attacked!
They might leave any minute!
Aliens won’t come for
just this much trash.
Where’s the superhero
for the aliens to come!
Son…pass me my teeth please.
Here, everyone's grandpas are boxing and
you can’t even pick up your own teeth!
Bro, even my grandpa wants to fight.
Hey…he’s too old!
Will end up losing his teeth.
There’s nothing to
worry about the teeth.
They are already fake.
We can get new ones.
Put my name down too.
What’s more important is fighting itself.
Not win or loss.
Poor chap…
really wanted to fight a boxing match.
If he could have fought,
he’d have left with respect.
Bro, let's put our names down,
else the kids won’t let us live in peace.
You’re right!
What grandpa…
you're lifting such puny weights!
Lift some heavy weights…
Be a MAN!!
Yes.
Okay…just a minute!
Now give it your all!
Heyy….anyone!!
Help!!
Here is a list of 12 people who are
participating in the boxing championship.
If the championship happens in the school,
then all the kids will see it.
And they will all feel
very proud that even at this age,
their grandfathers have
the spirit in them to fight.
Nice!
Nice initiative!
There’s a doubt sir.
Bearing our ages in mind,
if anyone gets hurt,
then it might affect the kids adversely,
even the school.
You are so powerful;
then what are YOU worried about?!
I was just saying it for everyone.
Now it’s a matter of our honour.
Either we fight or we die!
We won’t die,
we will be martyred!
We will pass on with honour.
Err…why don’t we race instead sir?
Sporting spirit can still be reflected in that.
Fighting will only showcase violence.
- EXCUSE ME !
Boxing is a sport;
it is not fighting. Mind It!
Sir…he’s right.
Let’s have a race.
Deepu’s grandpa will not let you win.
It is not about win or loss;
it is about fighting
Yeah yeah…have your fun;
make a fool of me.
Careful…careful…
Now, you must do what I tell you.
You will have to try to finish first.
But if you can’t then it doesn’t matter;
just finish last.
Not even second;
either first or last.
Why?!
- All’s good if you finish first.
But if you finish last then I will tell everyone
that you did it for the sake of everyone else.
Got it?
Either first or…?
Last.
Bravo!
Go!
Hello... Hello...
Good Morning Children!
You are all welcome
to this exciting race!
You see, in this race first
or last are not that important.
Running is what is important.
Organization of such an event….
[announcement fades]
Grandpa should have raced
with people of his level.
A superhero racing with them?!
If only the aliens had arrived on time,
we wouldn’t have to witness all of this.
[announcement] Whoever participates today,
is already a winner for us.
So let’s find out then,
who becomes today’s- Super Grandpa!
So ready…Get…Set…and…
C’mon sir…
Grandfather seems to
be really pumped up!
Why do Earth people
drive in slow motion?
This is their actual speed.
Oh…so slow!
Sister’s call!
Hello Sister!
- Where have you reached?
Sister, we are on a bus;
on our way.
On a bus?!
Where’s your spaceship?
Err…we had parked in the wrong place
so it got towed.
Super…you can’t even
take care of a spaceship?!
Sister we don’t have the permissions.
They are asking for some PAN of Aadhaar.
Aadhaar of PAN.
They are asking for an Aadhaar of PAN.
There’s been an overthrow
of the regime here. Look up!!
What?!
- The enemy forces have left.
Hey…what are you doing?
You will die yourself
and get others killed too!
Sorry…sorry…sorry.
Moron, you shouldn’t
spit on the Earth!
Shameless!
Could you please drive
a little faster, brother?
Here…you drive!
I drove off in my car,
Ready…get…set…
and…[whistle!]
C’mon Grandpa run!
I drove off in my car,
On the way, not too far,
Sachin’s grandfather is walking
at the last position….er…running!
My honour’s all spoiled.
I left my heart behind at that spot.
Kartar sir is in the lead!
Surprise !!
Sachin’s grandfather has left the rest
of the grandfathers behind and is in the lead!
Bravo !!
Hey…what are you doing lying down!
C’mon...
get up Grandfather!
You were saying that
your Grandpa is a national level sportsman.
That’s what he had said.
All grandpas have made
up their own stories.
Kartar Singh sir is up and running…
C’mon, run, run!!
I woke up, and ran off.
Almost reaching the finishing line…
I leaped across every barrier,
…and he wins!!
At the second place is
Sachin’s grandfather.
I left my heart behind at that spot
Our Super Grandpa for
the day is Kartar Singh sir!
They won because of you.
And I feel that
you too should get a prize.
You are a winner too!
After zero, we have
a new invention in our class, Superzero!
Farter, Farter, who’s a Farter?
- Deepu’s Grandfather, Deepu’s Grandfather!
There is no superhero afterall.
Now we will have to make do
watching this fight only.
You don’t worry, okay.
Once Grandpa gets powers...
...then along with the aliens,
we will rough them up too.
I have been lying.
There’s no superhero.
Grandpa’s a Superzero only.
When I joined newly,
I didn’t know how to make friends.
That’s why I lied.
Sorry.
Deepu,
remember…
strong friendships are built
only when you tell the truth.
We shouldn’t write on walls.
If we tell everyone,
then powers are lost, right...
But where’s the power, eh?
Then we should definitely write!
There should be complete insult.
Write!
Deepu’s …Grandpa…Super…
Hero!!
Who’s Grandpa is a superhero?
Deepu’s Grandpa.
At least, that's what he says!
Alright, let’s check and confirm.
Are you an alien?
How did you know?
Now we know everything!
Who’s a superhero; and who’s an alien!!
Hey, we really are aliens!
Are you really an alien?
- YES!
Alright then,
show us how you fly.
We shouldn’t waste time now.
- Yes.
Hey! Shut up!
Believe us now?
What’s your next plan?
There’s going to be
an attack on Earth
Please, please get me down!
Mom is calling me.
I have to do my homework.
MOM!! MOM!!!
Him!
That’s him!!
And who’s that next to him?
This is an alien.
He had ordered a picture with him.
Still hasn’t paid.
This is an alien?!
Are aliens like this?!
Have a little decency bro!
At least have some respect
for people from other planets.
Later you will be whining
about aliens attacking!!
You wanna attack him?
Oh no! Let’s go there first.
That’s more important. C’mon !
Want to attack just anywhere?!
Call Grandpa over.
There’s a surprise for him.
Look…that’s him who has been
calling himself a superhero.
And they…are aliens!
Completely original;
just landed!
Attack!!
Huh..!!
How can we believe
that they are aliens?
Yes! We are aliens.
- Ya! We are aliens.
And we don’t lie.
Namaste !
Namskar !
We are from Superearth-
which is left from the moon, after 5 lakh kilometers
a right and then after two planets left again.
Upper or lower?
- Upper.
East or West?
- West.
Neighbourhood?
- PSX-03.
Ajar-Bajar?
Jiju (Brother-in-Law) !!!
Super!! He is the superhero!
Dad, you kept such
a huge thing from us;
that you are a superhero!!
Would you have believed
it if I had told you?
I told these two;
did you believe?
Keep on testing; making me run;
getting me to box!
Now see…both these aliens are
saying that I am a superhero!
Ask them!
Okay okay…
accepted.
But now that the aliens are here,
can you show us a little bit of flying?
How does one fly bro?
Don’t worry Jiju,
we will have you practice it; right?
Jiju?
- Jiju.
Our Sister still loves Jiju a lot.
Even now.
- Even now.
Musi.
Yeahh…alien.
Orange candy…
- Yes.
Oh wow!
My mother in law is an alien?
Mother didn’t come?
She will be.
Oh wow! Now we have relatives
on another planet as well!!
Don’t make fun.
Your Earth is in danger.
You have to prepare for war now.
War ?
Attack.
There’s going to be an attack on Earth.
Why attack?
Dad…do you still have something
going on with the alien-mom?
No no...
she was just in my dreams yesterday.
That’s not the issue.
We have had a regime change.
The Army has taken
control over everything.
The people of our planet
want to capture Earth.
They have already left.
By the morning,
the attack would happen here.
Dad, let’s go from here.
Start Packing.
- Uncle! What are you saying?
Did we waste our time over nothing?
Now Grandpa will
definitely have to fight.
Hey!
You’ll fight?!
When did I say that
I am a superhero?
I don’t have any powers.
Dad, why did you
take the powers?
Couldn’t you have asked us once?
You want to play the hero too!
Uncle. The doctor has prohibited
him from lifting weights.
Back problem…knee problem…
BP…Sugar; he’s got them all.
Last time he had a fight
with the vegetable vendor
his BP was high for 2 days!
Dear niece, you will
have to fight this war.
He is indeed the true superhero of the Earth.
Only he has that power.
I have that power?
If not in you,
then not in anybody.
You are the protector of the Earth.
When you are the protector, why to fear?!
Tell me,
what is to be done.
First of all, you look up.
On your target;
till where you have to fly.
Good.
Now jump.
Then you will fly.
Hey..hey...
what are you saying bro.
Wanna get me killed or what?
Let’s go step by step.
First, 1 foot, then 10 feet
and then we’ll see.
If I look down,
then I get dizzy.
Oh don’t be afraid.
Firstly, think that
you are a superhero.
I have been thinking just
that since I was a kid.
Grandpa, not with doubt
but with confidence.
Now it is already proven
that you are a superhero.
Yes Dad!
You are a superhero!
Parrot…
- Fly!
Mynah…
Superhero!
Oh I can’t do it !
Not happening !
Seems like Grandpa’s
powers have expired.
That’s alright.
No worries.
This time we
will support a little.
3-2-1-
- Take Off!!
Bro..Aaaaarrghhh…
what are you doing?!
Deepu!!
Hey hey…get me down!
Get me down!!!!
VERY GOOD!
NOW YOU WILL HAVE
TO FLY ON YOUR OWN!
How do I fly on my own?!
Are you mad?!!
I AM STOPPING MY SUPPORT.
Deepu…
- OKAY?
Deepu…ask him
o get me down!!!
READY!
1-2-
Swear on your Sister…
- FLYYYY!!!
Aargghhhhh.!!!!!
A little further lower bro!
Killed me!
Broke my back...
You should meet
Saksham’s grandpa once too.
I think he might be the superhero.
Else, we will be
in trouble tomorrow.
Painkiller…would be a little relief.
I feel that his powers
will manifest only in battle.
Alien uncle,
give these powers to me, I’ll manage.
Hey hey…power is given upon
seeing the worth of a person;
it’s not a mere offering
Grandpa…what are you doing?
Get up!
Rouse your powers.
You have the power!
You are a SUPERHERO!!
Grandpa!!
Wake up your POWER!!!!
WAKE IT UP!!!
You are right.
If not now, then never.
I’ll get martyred
Dad, why will YOU get martyred?
I will get martyred.
Uncle, we can’t get emotional.
We will have to be practical.
You are not the superhero.
He is.
You can get martyred.
Everyone will have to be told that
they shouldn’t get out of their homes tomorrow.
This task I will do.
as you can see,
how it was just word earlier,
and then curses started,
and now it’s a fistfight.
Brother, how are you feeling?
Umm…err..it feels very nice.
Earlier when they were not fighting,
it was a bit boring.
But when uncle slapped,
it was very nice, very interesting sir!
Oh Dad!
What are you doing?
Son, I am war-reporting.
But dad, real war is
happening there; come quickly!
Let’s go.
Dad! This is alien uncle.
Namaste !
- Namaste !
I am Khulasa and war-reporter.
The kids were scared.
- Thank you.
He was saying that there’s going
to be an attack on Earth tomorrow?
You heard it right.
You want to do an exposé?
- Yes.
Switch on your camera.
Sure
Ohh…this has become…
kind of different!
As in, it is kind of ghost-like.
As in, ghosts too are invisible on camera
but can be seen otherwise.
Up…up...
Yess…one more…
Didn’t I tell you, he’s the superhero.
He will save us from the attack tomorrow.
Aaarghh…
Well, now that you are saying it,
then let’s believe it!
Nice to meet you sir.
Mr. Khulasa...
...please help us.
Please tell everyone not to
leave their homes after 8. Please.
Not 8, they are coming at 9.
Oh Nanu (grandpa)...only if we say 8
then people will be indoors by 9.
This is India.
Oh nice, interesting fact!
I didn’t know that.
Now, c’mon…
Can I ask a question?
Yes.
Why do you always
come to ATTACK the Earth?
No. Never.
We have never attacked Earth.
This has always been our favourite planet.
It has water, air, plants
and trees, and life.
Many years ago,
we used to live here only.
The grandfather of our great grandfather had
2 personal dinosaurs of his own- Hira & Moti.
But when asteroids crashed here,
we had to vacate out of fear.
And we settled a new planet of our own.
Be practical.
But the people of our planet feel
that you all don’t care for your Earth.
You cut down trees,
spread filth and trash.
But…for this, why are you coming to
fight all the way from so very far?
We will take care of it.
I’ll just make an awareness video
on social media and that’s that!
No.
It’s gotten much worse.
We feel that you all are
not worthy of Earth.
That’s why they are coming
to remove you from Earth.
Then…what can we do?
- Fight.
If you win,
then maintain cleanliness.
And if you don’t win then…
- Then…
They will clean us up!
Yeah, correct.
And, HE’s the one to save us?!
Do you happen to
have a special approach?
Not yet, but maybe
he’ll have it at the time of battle.
And if you don’t get it?
I’ll fight;
with whatever strength I have.
This is the chance.
Since childhood I was waiting to do something
that would make everyone say wow.
Mother used to say that,
when opportunity comes,
then never step back.
Do something so good that people say,
‘Wow! What a deed!’
It’s not important if
I have power or don’t have it.
They are coming to fight ME,
that’s important.
Tomorrow if I fall during the fight,
then before I die, do come
and say ‘Bravo’ in my ear.
I have no desire of being a superhero.
But I do like hearing my praise.
Sorry grandpa...
- What happened? why are you crying ?
Hey... Hey Laddu !
Hey laddu,
Where are you going?
Nothing will happen to Grandpa, right?
I don’t want this fight.
I am fine with
just listening to stories.
It is time.
You will have to save everyone tomorrow.
Only you can save.
Dad, please give me 20 rupees.
It’s a bit urgent.
But I will return it.
Had stolen one day.
Returning it now.
God! Please take care
of things tomorrow.
Grandpa…
- Yes.
It is 7:15.
Dad, come back a winner.
And take care of your back.
What are you doing here dear?
Can I come with you too?
I want to fight too.
Not visible yet.
Are they cancelling their plan?!
I have even declared it on my channel!
Good…not many
would have seen it.
Hey, what are you saying…
there were 72 views just 10 mins ago.
Dad! You saw it 70 times
and I saw it twice.
There they are!
Jiju...
- Yes.
Touch here.
Did you feel anything?
No.
Seems like Grandpa’s touch is broken.
As you can’t see, aliens have arrived.
We don’t know what will happen.
I will keep reporting
the news minute to minute.
Exposé King Kannu,
from the doors of death!
What’s the matter?
Why are they not coming out?
Must have slept off.
- What?
They came all this way to sleep?
They must be jetlagged
travelling from one planet to another;
that’s why they must have slept off.
Here he is.
He is the one.
After capturing our planet,
his target is Earth.
Jiju…please go.
Without power?
Oh just go,
you’ll get it.
Jiju!
- Yes.
Just keep one thing in mind.
If things get messy,
then make sure you attack first,
only then you will get your power.
And what if
I don’t get the power?
[together] Point!
More than them,
I am getting scared of you two!
SUPERHERO JAGDISH CHANDRA! HAIL!
[all together] HAIL!!
- Keep all the Hails for later.
Make sure you water the plants.
And the insurance is in the kids’ names.
GO JIJU GO!
YOU CAN DO IT!
Yes yes…
I will do it.
As you can see…our superhero,
with his plant, is going towards the alien.
Umm..myself…Jagdish.
I am a superhero.
Welcome to Earth.
This Earth has been ours
and we do not need any welcome.
These trees were
planted by our ancestors.
We are the same only.
We have carefully kept
the Earth given by you sir.
By cutting the trees?
By spreading garbage?
By spoiling the oceans?
Yes sir.
We have made a mistake but…
Tch tch tch…
your time is over.
Now we will HAVE to return
to Earth or you will destroy it.
Oh why aren’t they fighting?
Just whiling away time.
These aliens, as they talk,
attack all of a sudden!
all of a sudden!
GRANDPA!
JUST ATTACK!
Hey! Shut up!
Don’t you see son,
two elders are talking.
You gave powers to the wrong guy!
They are right;
we are not here to just talk.
You are wasting
your and my time.
GRANDPA! THE ONE WHO
WILL STRIKE FIRST WILL WIN!
C’MON STRIKE!!
Just attack!
HEY…ONLY WHEN YOU ATTACK
WILL YOU GET YOUR POWERS!!
Yes!
Did he get the power?
- No!
Now Grandpa is done for!
Sir, I am extremely sorry sir!
This…this happened automatically sir.
By mistake my hand slipped…
it ..my..mistake slipped out of my hand.
By mistake my hand hit you sir.
Hey!!
And it starts!
HEY!! HOW DARE YOU TOUCH GRANDPA!!
HOW DARE YOU!!
Wait you…son of an Alien!
Just you wait!
Hey Uncle! The office is closed.
The aliens have arrived.
First save your life.
You can get your pension tomorrow as well.
Wait!!
- Let go alien Uncle!
Don’t be afraid.
You have to fight.
I am with you.
You are a ray of hope.
Rise now.
Thrive now.
Soar ,towards the sky.
Awaken the storm brewing within you.
You don’t need to bow down to fear anymore.
Lands and skies tell your tales.
Buckle up. It’s time to break
every norm you know.
Rise now, fight now.
Declare war.
Wreck havoc.
Rise now .
That’s him! Our Superhero is here!
Yesss!
Fate will dance to your tunes.
Whoaaa!!
Looks like Grandpa’s power is gone!
Power didn’t go,
it has come!
Fate will dance to your tunes.
The skies will fall at your command.
Give yourself a chance my friend.
Destiny awaits your victory.
And now the more he fights,
the more his powers will increase.
His weaknesses will
also become his strengths.
The skies will fall at your command.
Give yourself a chance my friend.
Destiny awaits your victory.
[together] Yess!!
Can I fight too?
Uncle..c’mon this is cheating!
You found me first!
Yes, but she needs it now.
Uncle…can we too
get some small powers?
On the next visit.
By then we will be old!
Friends, if we win
then swear to it that...
...we will keep the Earth clean
and will grow trees.
Hail Mother India!
Surely on the next visit, right?
- Yes.
Swear on your mother!
- Sure.
Hey! come back.
Hey! Where are you going bro?!
That’s Sri Lanka!
Uncle, is there any power which
lets you pass exams without studying?
GRANDPA!
Hope you didn’t get hurt.
Hey!
Don’t you touch the kid!
YOU CANNOT DO THIS!
Alright guys!
This is the end…
before dying…Like…Share…
Subscribe…Khulasa News.
Lord Hanuman! Grandpa needs
Your superpowers now.
Grandpa, get up!
GRANDPA!
Grandpa, you are our only hope!
Grandpa, wake up!
Hail lord Hanuman
Brave and Great!
YAAARRHHHHHHHH!!
[reverberating]
[together] YESS!!
Hail Lord Hanuman
What is this?
X-43.
As dangerous as your atom bomb!
Grandpa!!
GRANDPA!!
Grandpa!
Grandpa, get up!
YOU are our superhero!
Please get up Grandpa! Please!
Grandpa!
Grandpa Bravo!
BRAVO grandpa!
Please Grandpa, get up!
Bravo Grandpa! Bravo!
And that night, once again a ship arrived.
But this time, it was Deepu’s Grandma’s.
Means our garndpa’s Musi
Namaste!
- Namaste Grandma!
Namaste mother.
Welcome home!
Now Grandpa is switching from his Superhero
mode to a slightly romantic mode.
You have grown up!
You have grown old too!
Just one thing went wrong.
And the next day,
Deepu’s father got transferred.
When the aliens come back again,
we will meet again!
Laddu…
let me give you a superpower.
The more you study,
the more marks you score.
Grandpa…
will miss you a lot.
Today, both of my best friends were leaving…
I was feeling bad
but Grandpa has promised
that we’ll meet in no time
Actually I never doubt anything
our Superhero Grandpa says,
because Superhero never lies.
While leaving Grandpa had said
the aliens would be back soon…
with double the trouble.
I hope they do return,
if not I might have to become
a pensioner (geriatric) Superhero like Grandpa too!
Laddu…how are you?
Oh I got your call!
I am first class!
Had to speak to you about something important;
hope there’s no one around you.
No.
Congratulations!
You are going to be a superhero!
Get ready!
The aliens are on their way!
Hey !
You are my cub, kiddo
Don’t go by my looks,
white hair, wrinkled skin
Don’t go by my walk,
Even if I waddle in.
Hey Buddy
You aren’t a mere panther...
You are a Tiger’s father!
Don’t go by my looks,
white hair, wrinkled skin
Don’t go by my walk,
Even if I waddle in.
Don’t go by my age,
Don’t go by my pills .
Up my sleeve ,
I’ve got tricks and skills.
This walking stick becomes,
a staff for my flag of victory.
My Backache made an exit,
My powers made an entryyyyyyy.
Look Look Look
Here comes our Superhero
Superhero Grandpop.
He’ll make you cry non-stop.
Great grand Superhero!
Here comes our buddy.
Buddy
He’ll deep clean this earth
The environment will be neat
AQI
He’ll plant many trees
And give you a fruit treat
Grandpop is my Power
This power is so solid
Power that flies a rocket without fuel
God’s blessings rest on his locket
Granpop is our charger
No electricity needed for this socket
Bow down
Touch his feet
Here comes Superhero Grandpop
He’s your pop’s pop
Beating bad guys non-stop
Here comes Superhero, Superhero,
Superhero Grandpop
He’ll make you cry non-stop.
Great grand Superhero!
Here he comes buddy
Ikkadi Paka Ikkadi Poko
Make way for Grandpop